Why are you the only one here?
Didn't I tell you?
Fu's cover song,
Tokage's gambling,
Ichiko's cooking,
and your mukbang...
Since your solo content's been gaining steam,
it's time to put more effort
into videos with everybody.
I-I feel ya.
Sorry. They're all out at the moment.
Out, you say?
Even though I pulled an all-nighter
to finish my editing work
in time for today's shoot?
Well, you know how it is.
No, I don't!
Do you not care?!
You think you're hot stuff because
your solo vids are doing okay?
Get real!
Sorry—
I've had it!
You're not getting my blood!
Please!
Don't abandon me!
I'll do anything you want!
Anything?
Then go take a trip here by yourselves!
Tra-Pickle Island?
A Must for This Summer!
Desert Island Booking Plan
Tra-Pickle Island
Whole Island Rental!
A once-in-a-lifetime memory!
Want to experience
the ultimate adventure?
Highlights of
Tra-Pickle Island
A one-week desert island survival challenge.
What?
Normally, you need special permission
to film on a desert island
You'll be taking care of all the
planning and filming by yourselves,
so bring me back a proper video!
Good night!
Hey! Masaki!
What even goes into a proper video?
Blood-or-Die! Desert Island Survival
The ocean!
The sandy beach!
A desert island!
Hey, what's with that attitude?!
Another thousand yen and I would have had it.
Why'd I get dragged out here?
I was in the middle of my shift.
And I was in the middle of shopping for dinner!
But now that we're here,
we might as well enjoy it!
L-Live-sama!
All eyes on me!
MayoPan's
One-Week Desert Island
Survival Challenge
This is MayoPan's one-week
desert island survival challenge!
MayoPan's
One-Week Desert Island
Survival Challenge
Here's the agenda for day one!
Day One
Set up camp
Start a fire
Collect drinking water
Day One
Set up camp
Start a fire
Collect drinking water
Leveling the ground!
Gathering flotsam!
Breaking a sweat putting up a tent!
Getting blisters while using a hand drill friction,
until at last, we start a fire!
Exploring the area until
we find potable water!
Collecting and boiling it!
Tasty!
Day two!
Struggling to catch fish in the water to eat!
A perfect set of plans, as proper as can be!
Come back!
Come back, Masaki's blood!
That's all!
The End
Any questions?
Do we really gotta do all that?
I wanna take it easy.
Tokage!
Live-sama spent good time planning this!
Not my problem.
Here!
Surviving on a desert island in swimsuits!
This is guaranteed to rake in the clicks!
And if we strike it rich...
You can play all the
pachinko and slots you want!
Or sing all you want with a pro live band!
Or, er... eat all the snacks you want?
Let's do this, girls!
A perfect motivational speech, too!
Recording
Day 1
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch!
Live here!
Ichiko!
I'm Fu.
Tokage!
Ichiko, Tokage.
Take this seriously.
Aye aye!
As of today...
We'll be starting a one-week,
girls-only desert island survival challenge!
And of course, it'll be survival in the
dead of night, the MayoPan way!
Let's get down to business
with our plans for the first day!
Today, we'll be setting up camp using flotsam.
I can build anything,
from a castle to a log cabin—
This will be our home base!
There's plenty of space,
and it should be easy to level out.
Perfect for setting up camp!
Okay!
We've got a lot of work ahead
starting from day one!
Let's get pumped up!
Here we go!
Yeah.
Wonder if that's what they're
saying right about now.
Man, TSUMA-shi's good!
His editing here is so slick!
Oh, wow!
Night-vision mode works better than I thought!
Very nice.
Boy, flotsam is pretty hard to find, huh?
Oh, right now, everyone else
is preparing to set up camp.
And that's why...
Huh?
Whoa!
Look at this!
A tarp!
Just what we need to protect us
from the rain and wind!
Wait, there's driftwood here as well!
Sweet!
Tomatoes
A can and a plastic bottle, too!
Awesome, no punctures!
We can use this to collect water,
and cook on the campfire with this can,
and even make salt from seawater!
The perfect find for some peace of mind!
With that, I've got what I need!
Time to head back to base!
Recording
So heavy...
I'm dying here!
The more shots, the better.
Recording
I'm back!
Welcome back, Live-sama!
The hell's this?!
The perfect base, of course!
It's DIY! D-I-Y!
You really built a house?!
What happened to survival?!
Live-sama, I made sure to get all of it!
Heave-ho, heave-ho!
I think you've exceeded the
limits of human ability.
I'm so sad.
This...
turned into this!
All my hard work...
All right, here we go!
Let's go all out and start this fire!
Listen up, everyone.
The struggle to start a fire
is what matters here.
Even survival pros can take hours just to...
You can start a fire in no time!
How amusing.
Not if you're human, you can't!
Live-sama, how's this?
Fu, you get it!
I-It's working!
Ichiko, the dry grass!
Here, dry grass!
Thanks.
Dang, you're a real natural, Fu.
You did it!
Good job!
I forgot to press record.
What a slow trickle.
Slow as molasses.
Slow and steady.
Listen, people want to see—
If we crack this baby open,
the water'll come shooting out!
Mayonaka Pun—
You know you can't just punch
a rock in half, right?
R-Right.
Tomatoes
Okay, let's start boiling this.
Why are you drinking it?!
Huh?
You need to boil the water before drinking it!
If you were human,
you'd be in for a really bad time!
But I'm a vampire—
Ah!
Tee-hee!
Instead of Drinking Water,
We Ate Only
Watermelon
For 1 Whole Week
Managed to get it done.
Back
Publish
I wonder how they're all doing.
Not that I'm expecting much.
Whatever. Time for a drink!
Tokage!
They sure are a handful.
Day 2
Ta-dah!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Recording
This is day two of life on a desert island!
Today, we're diving into the water
to catch some fish!
Who will be the first to snag one?
Okay, let's get started!
Now...
Where the hell did they go?!
Here?
If you don't, then who will?
You're MayoPan's star singer, Fu!
S-Star singer...
Okay! Take it away!
Take it away!
Okay, please listen!
Are ya ready?
Here we go!
Okay, place yer bets!
Even on 2-2, huh?
Then I'll go for odd on 4-1!
Open!
Even on 2-2?!
I lost!
Got myself a coconut crab.
Here we go!
Got it! I'm first!
Hi-yah!
Victory!
You're going way too wild!
There's no way humans could catch a marlin!
The bigger the better!
No way!
What's the big deal?
Hell, why are we even on this desert island?
To shoot a video, what else?!
Let's do this the right way!
We barely have any usable footage
from the past two days!
She's right.
You two need to take it down a notch.
I don't want to hear that from you!
You were about to sing, too!
That's not relevant right now.
How sassy!
I don't need sass from you, Fu!
What's that mean?!
You're my lackey!
Ugh, I'm starving. Time for some blood.
That's not true!
Do you understand me?!
Huh?
What is it?
What now?
The blood... isn't here!
We forgot to bring it.
Next, we have the weather.
Typhoon Warning
The typhoon that formed in the Philippine Sea
yesterday continues to grow stronger,
Typhoon Warning
Tra-Pickle Island
Extremely Strong
Storm Area
Strong Wind Area
and is currently passing through
the Tra-Pickle Island region.
Everyone, this way!
Yay!
Now then, let's set all this up!
I want some blood!
You know we don't have any!
Well, why not?!
Calm down!
I wish I could!
Blood! Where's my blood?!
Why don't we film today's part for now?
Day 3
Recording
T-Ta-dah!
Day three on a desert island!
Today, we'll be, um...
Tokage!
Sorry, but I'm getting outta here!
Too low on blood.
I know! My phone!
I'll call for help on my phone!
No service!
No Service
I need...
I need to go home!
The parlor is getting new machines!
I asked Ichijo-kun to tune the pins!
Chance Akaishi's waiting for me!
I know! A raft!
No!
I'm all out of ideas.
Blood... I want blood.
If I sing...
Even if I sing a song,
I still can't distract myself!
Hey! It'll be okay!
I'm sure Masaki will notice
and come to our rescue!
Let's focus on shooting our video until then!
'Kay?
Day 4
Live-sama.
Live-sama!
There!
Day 5
Staying Up Late
on a Sunday
Day 6
Tokage's finally gone into
low-energy mode as well.
Day 7
Lighting, check!
Camera angle, check!
Let's get to it!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch...
Setup, check.
In the end, nothing turned out
the way I planned.
But I need to finish the job, at least!
Recording
Live here!
We're finally done with our
seven-day survival challenge!
Good work, everyone!
We ran into all sorts of
mishaps this time around.
There's a lot we didn't get around to doing.
Let's think of those as future goals for now.
Recording
Next time, we'll prepare more thoroughly.
For a more perfect time surviving...
Surviving...
Okay, everyone, until next time.
Day 8
The week's up,
so why aren't they back yet?
We still need to record
their closing remarks—
Ow!
What's this?!
This is their supply.
Wait, what?!
Does that mean they left this behind?!
Can they go without blood for a week?
So cold...
I just wish I could've tasted
Masaki's blood before the end.
Masaki...
Huh?
I can go ahead?
At long last!
I get to drink Masaki's blood!
Time to dig in!
Live.
Live!
How's it going?
Wh-What are you doing here?!
What kind of question is that?!
You're the ones who forgot to bring the blood!
Talk about causing trouble.
Shige?!
Do you know how hard it is to fly
across the ocean carrying a human?
You there!
Crying won't work on me next time!
H-Huh?!
Can you stop making stuff up?!
You upside-down liar!
You're the one who was crying
about how they might be dead.
Upside-down or not.
Gimme some more blood!
You already had plenty!
Please stop fighting!
I-I didn't cry or anything.
Hey, now! Wait your turn!
Live?
What's wrong?
I wasn't able to shoot a proper video at all.
I'm nothing but a failure!
Hey, just calm down.
I can't show you any of the footage we shot!
Scrap it! Throw it away!
I'm sorry!
I already watched it.
Skimmed it, at least.
Why'd you look?!
It's good stuff.
What?
Chopping down a tree bare-handed won't fly,
but starting the fire in a flash,
or drinking untreated water...
You even managed to put up a tent.
Right?
But we can't use most of it!
It's totally absurd, not to mention
beyond human ability.
There are plenty of editing tricks
we can use for that.
You need material that's entertaining
before anything else.
But there was also the marlin,
and then the typhoon.
Most of the back half is just us half-dead.
It's just one disaster after another.
What's wrong with disasters?
You don't end up half-dead every day.
You got real lucky!
That's totally off!
You can't make a proper video like that!
No, sure you can.
What?
Maybe it didn't go the way you planned it,
but it shows you all trying your hardest.
All of that taken as a whole
is what makes for a good video.
Like the time with the garlic.
You did a proper good job.
Then I'm...
All good.
Does that mean...
I can drink your blood?
Not what we agreed on.
Ah, okay.
Still, looks like you need me
in charge after all.
I'll need to roll up my sleeves
to edit this bad boy!
I'll...
I'll help you edit it!
I'll do what I can with your help!
Let me warn you:
You need a real good eye for editing.
If you half-ass it, I'm calling off that
promise about my blood for good!
No problem!
I'm a real go-getter when it comes to it!
Happy to have you!
Live
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
Live here!
Masaki.
Can't believe we forgot the blood!
Nearby Residents Concerned
Lives in Vicinity
It suddenly collapsed and scared me to death
That's the most important thing!
Tsk, tsk. That's where you're wrong!
Huh?
The most important thing to me is Masaki...
Yeah, yeah.
...'s blood!
It always comes back to that!
Next time: "Ichiko's Wish"!
Ichiko's Wish
I wanna drink your blood!